Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2016 Campaign
  - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 2016
    - Blue pin American shield, words: One Nation United and Strong - From Sea to Shining Sea, We Must Be One America, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-052)
    - Red pin USA outline, words: It Is Time America! To Take Care of our Own from Sea To Shining Sea, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-053)
    - Blue pin photograph of Clinton head over USA, words: From First Lady to First Woman, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-054)
    - Large pin photograph of Clinton, words: K-12 education, criminal justice reform, social security and medicine, gun violence prevention, small business, racial justice..., 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-055)
    - Blue pin, H with arrow, words: hillaryclinton.com, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-056)
    - Large pin with colorful H, words: family, possible, change, diversity, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-057)
    - Large pin with red HC 2016, words: Hillary For America, America For Hillary (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-058)
    - Large pin rainbow colors, words: Equal Rights #HILLYES, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-059)
    - Large pin photograph of Clinton, black and white, words: Smart Tested Ready, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-060)
    - Large pin, words: Hillary Clinton (Into red), 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-061)
    - Large pin, red and blue, words: Hillary Prepared (Prep blue), 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-062)
    - Large pin with blue button, words: Pantsuits For President 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-063)
    - Large pin, light blue and dark blue, words: So My Daughter Knows She Can Be President. Hillary 16, 2016 (Box 26, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-064)
    - Large pin, light blue and dark blue, words: Fight Like Hill, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-065)
    - Large pin, purple, words: Vote, For Us., 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-066)
    - Large pin, dark blue, words: Every Child 2016 (HIL in dark blue) (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-067)
    - Blue pin, words; Hillary repeated in red white and blue, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-068)
    - Large pin with photograph of Clinton, black and white, words: Hillary Clinton 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-069)
    - Large blue pin with drawings of hands, words: HRC 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-070)
    - Red pin, words: She uses big words, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-071)
    - Light blue pin, words: She believes in science, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-072)
    - Dark blue pin, words: She does her homework, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-073)
    - Pin, red words: Hillary, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-074)
    - Pin, gray words: Rodham, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-075)
    - Pin, blue words: Clinton, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-076)
    - Pin red white and blue, photograph of Clinton head, black and white, word: Hillary, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-077)
    - Large pin, words: 45TH, Just A Matter of Time (H with arrow), 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-078)
    - Large pin with hammer, words: Shattering Ceilings Breaking Down Walls, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-079)
    - Large yellow pin with Rosie the Riveter, words: She Can Do It!, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-080)
    - Large pin, red and blue, words: My Body My Choice My Vote Hillary 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-081)
    - Large pin, light blue, words: Our Champion Hillary, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-082)
    - Pin with H arrow, dark blue, words: Clinton Kaine, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-083)
    - Pin with photograph of Clinton, black and white, words: We Made History, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-084)
    - Large pin, photograph of child drawing H with arrow, words: Our Future, 2016 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-085)
    - Button blue with American flag and text: Forward, together., 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-086)
    - Button black with text: She's Commander in Chief 45, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-087)
    - Button blue with printed image of Clinton text: I Trust Her, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-088)
    - Button blue with text: Hi!, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-089)
    - Button red with text: M.V.P. Most Vetted President, Hillary Clinton 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-090)
    - Button blue with H and text: Hillary 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-091)
    - Button blue with red and white dots and text: Hillary, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-092)
    - Button white with red and blue border and text: Hillary Trumps 'em all., 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-093)
    - Button pink and blue with multiple close-up photographs of Clinton with text: Shattered ceilings repair U.S., 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-094)
    - Button white with text: Honor America, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-095)
    - Button white with text: Heal America, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-096)
    - Button white with text: Heart America, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-097)
    - Button white with text: Hillary and Justice, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-098)
    - Button white with text: Hillary for All, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-099)
    - Button white with text: Hillary with Liberty, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-100)
    - Button red with white arrows and text: Empathy Hillary 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-101)
    - Button blue with white arrow and text: Progress Hillary 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-102)
    - Button blue with red arrow and text: Unity Hillary 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HRC2016-103)
  - Johnson, Gary Earl, 2016
    - Button blue, with text: Governor Gary Johnson for President, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-GEJ2016-001)
    - Button blue with eagle head and text: you in?, 2016 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-GEJ2016-002)
    - Sticker: you in?, 2016 (Box 16)
  - Sanders, Bernard, 2016
    - Button with text: Bernie 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-001)
    - Button with text: Bernie 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-002)
    - Button with happy face, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-003)
    - Button with text: Bernie, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-004)
    - Button with text: Bernie, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-005)
    - Button with text: Feel the Bern, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-006)
    - Button with drawing of Bernie Sanders and text: Feel the Bern, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-BXS2016-007)
  - Trump, Donald John, 2016
    - Button with printed color photograph of Trump and text: Donald Trump 2016 Make America Great Again!! (Box 12, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-001)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Trump and text: Trump 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-002)
    - Button with text: Hillary for Prison 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-003)
    - Button with text: Trump Make America Great Again!, 2016 (Box 12, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-004)
    - Red hat with embroidered text: Make America Great Again Trump 2016 (Box 18, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-005)
    - Button red with state of Ohio and text: Ohio for Trump, The Buckeye State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-006)
    - Button white with state of Virginia and text: Virginia for Trump, The Old Dominion State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-007)
    - Button white with state of Florida and text: Florida for Trump, The Sunshine State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-008)
    - Button white with state of Pennsylvania and text: Pennsylvania for Trump, The Keystone State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-009)
    - Button white with state of North Carolina and text: North Carolina for Trump, The Tar Heel State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-010)
    - Button red with state of Michigan and text: Michigan for Trump, The Great Lakes State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-011)
    - Button red with state of Florida and text: Florida for Trump, The Sunshine State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-012)
    - Button red with state of North Carolina and text: North Carolina for Trump, The Tar Heel State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-013)
    - Button white with text: Truth Trust Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-014)
    - Button red with gray border and text: Let's Reset Washington www.donaldjtrump.com, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-015)
    - Button white with red and white border and text: Trump Pence Make America Safe Again!, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-016)
    - Button pink T and text: Women for Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-017)
    - Button rainbow with text: LGBTQ for Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-018)
    - Button white with red and white border and text: Trump Pence Make America One Again!, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-019)
    - Button with color photo of Trump and text: Trump 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-020)
    - Button white with text: Travelgate #Hillaryforprison, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-021)
    - Button navy blue with text: #Make America Great Again, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-022)
    - Button white with red and white border and text: Trump Pence Make America Work Again!, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-023)
    - Button white with text: Truth Trust Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-024)
    - Button white with text: #BuildTheWall, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-025)
    - Button white with state of North Carolina and text: North Carolina for Trump, The Tar Heel State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-026)
    - Button white with state of North Carolina and text: North Carolina for Trump, The Tar Heel State, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-027)
    - Button red with text: Secret Server #Hillaryforprison, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-028)
    - Button black with text: Benghazi Cover-Up #Hillaryforprison, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-029)
    - Button black with white Hillary campaign logo and text: Hillary for Prison, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-030)
    - Button red with text: #Big League, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-031)
    - Button white with red and white border and text: Trump Pence Make America Great Again!, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-032)
    - Button white with red and white border and text: Trump Pence Make America Safe Again!, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-033)
    - Button red with text: #I'm With You, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-034)
    - Button white with text: #Yuge, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-035)
    - Button white with text: Clinton Foundation Scandals #Hillaryforprison, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-036)
    - Button red and blue, with text: Trump Pence 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-037)
    - Button oval with blue border, American flag, and color photo of Trump with text: Donald Trump 2016 Make America Great Again (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-038)
    - Pin gold made into text: I Like Mike, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-039)
    - Button yellow with figure with bag of money and text: Never Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-040)
    - Button yellow with figure with pacifier and text: Never Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-041)
    - Button yellow with figure with money in pockets and text: Never Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-042)
    - Button yellow with stick figure face of Trump, 2016 (Box 34, Item RL-00580-DJT2016-043)
    - Bumper sticker: Trump Pence: Make America Great Again, 2016 (Box 16)
  - Stein, Jill Ellen, 2016
    - Pin photograph of Stein, American flag, words: Jill Stein 2016 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-JES2016-001)
    - Pin white, green words: Jill 2016 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-JES2016-002)
    - Pin green, white words: Jill 2016 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-JES2016-003)
- Undated Material from Various Campaigns, 1800s-2000s
  - Grant, Ulysses S., 1860s or 1870s
    - Pin rectangle with portrait of Grant, 1868 or 1872 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-USG18xx-001)
    - Pin rectangle with portrait of Grant and ribbon attached, 1868 or 1872 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-USG18xx-002)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, 1880s or 1890s
    - Pin image of Harrison, 1888 or 1892 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-BXH18xx-001)
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1890s or 1900s
    - Pin portrait of Bryan, American flag surrounding, name printed over, 1896, 1900, or 1908 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJBxxxx-001)
    - Pin portrait of Bryan, name printed under, silver background, 1896, 1900, or 1908 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJBxxxx-002)
    - Pin portrait of Bryan, words: For President Wm. J. Bryan. Black and green background., 1896, 1900, or 1908 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJBxxxx-003)
  - McKinley, William, 1890s or 1900s
    - Pin large portrait of McKinley, American flag outside background, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-001)
    - Pin portrait of McKinley, American flag background, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-002)
    - Pin portrait of McKinley with name printed under, gold background, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-003)
    - Pin portrait of McKinley, with words In Memoriam. Black background., 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-004)
    - Pin with portrait and picture of tin canvas. Words Count Me For (McKinley) And A Full (tin canvas), 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-005)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, name printed under. American flag surrounding., 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-006)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, red blue and white stars background, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-007)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, American flag background, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-008)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, name printed under, American flag surrounding, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-009)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, words Protection Home Rule printed, white background., 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-010)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, gold background, American flag sides, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-011)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, gold background, American ribbon on top, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-012)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley, M.R.C. printed above, blue framed background, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-013)
    - Button with portrait of McKinley, gold framed, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-014)
    - Pin portrait of McKinley, words: The McKinley League State of New York printed, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-015)
    - Pin portrait of McKinley, name printed over, black and white, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-016)
    - Metal pin, American flag, metal stars and stripes shield, metal portrait McKinley with William McKinley printed under, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-017)
    - Pin American flag, tiny McKinley portrait in middle, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-018)
    - Pin flag with red white and blue, words N.Y. Press McKinley printed, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-019)
    - Metal cowboy hat, white ribbon, 1896 or 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXMxxxx-020)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1900s
    - Pin shaped like a cowboy hat with text: TR, 1904 or 1912 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-TXR19xx-001)
    - Shriner mechanical badge; hinged face reveals photograph of Roosevelt, 1904 or 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR19xx-002)
    - Pin gold, with colorized photograph of Roosevelt, 1904 or 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR19xx-003)
    - Pin gold, with American flag on sides and printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1904 or 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR19xx-004)
    - Pin with American flag border with colorized photograph of Roosevelt with text: Victory, 1904 or 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR19xx-005)
    - Silver buckle with text: Theodore Roosevelt for President, 1904 or 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR19xx-006)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1900s or 1910s
    - Button with printed photograph of Taft and text: Wm H. Taft of Ohio, 1908 or 1912 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-001)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-002)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, name printed under, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-003)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, sepia, name printed under, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-004)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, sepia, name printed under, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-005)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, red white blue stripes surrounding, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-006)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, sepia, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-007)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, color, light blue and white background, facing right, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-008)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, color, light blue and white background, facing left, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-009)
    - Pin portrait of Taft black and white, surrounded by red white and blue stripes and stars, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-010)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-011)
    - Blue pin with white horizontal stripe, Taft printed in stripe, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-012)
    - Navy blue pin, Taft written in gold, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-013)
    - Button portrait of Taft, words: Taft League of Massachusetts. White ribbon, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-014)
    - Triangle button, Red white and blue stars and stripes, words: Taft, on red. White ribbon., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-015)
    - Button navy blue, Taft printed in gold, white ribbon, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-016)
    - Button blue, Taft printed in faded gold, white ribbon, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-017)
    - Large pin portrait of Taft, black and white. Words: WM. H. Taft for President, under., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-018)
    - Pin with red white and blue flag. Portrait of Taft, black and white. Framed in metal, eagle on top., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-019)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, words: WM. H. Taft., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-020)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, colored, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-021)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-022)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, sepia, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-023)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white. Blue surrounding, words: Hello Bill., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-024)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, words: Wm. H. Taft of Ohio., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-025)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white. Words: The Safest, TAFT marked out in red., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-026)
    - Maroon pin, words: Taft in gold., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-027)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white, oval. American flag shield over, American flag ribbon under portrait., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-028)
    - Metal pin portrait of Taft, long needle., 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-029)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, red white and blue surrounding pattern, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-030)
    - Pin portrait of Taft, black and white. Gold frame. Words: For President Rm. H. Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-031)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-032)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-033)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-034)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-035)
    - Pin with colorized portrait of Taft with text: Kansas First Voters Taft League, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-036)
    - Pin with red, white, and blue border with printed photograph of Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-037)
    - Pin with gold rim and printed photograph of Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-038)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Taft and text: WM.H.Taft for President, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-039)
    - Pin with red, white, and blue stripes with text: Taft, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-040)
    - Pin with florid border and printed photograph of Taft suspended from American flag in shape of a bow, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-041)
    - Pin with colorized portrait of Taft suspended from leather belt, 1908 or 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-WHT19xx-042)
  - Debs, Eugene Victor, 1910s
    - Button with printed photograph of Debs and text: Debs, 1900, 1904, 1908, 1912, or 1920 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-EVD19xx-001)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1910s
    - Button with printed photographs of Wilson and Thomas Marshall, 1912 or 1916 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-001)
    - Button with printed photograph of Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-002)
    - Pin with back rim and printed photograph of Wilson with text: In Memoriam, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-003)
    - Pin with printed photographs of Wilson, King of Belgium, Cardinal Mercier, with text: We have loved justice, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-004)
    - Pin blue, with text: I am for Wilson and an 8 hour day, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-005)
    - Pin blue, with text: I am for Wilson and an 8 hour day, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-006)
    - Pin with color portrait of Wilson and text: Woodrow Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-007)
    - Pin white with printed photograph of Wilson with text: Win with Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-008)
    - Pin (small) with printed photograph of Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-009)
    - Pin with gold rim and printed photograph of Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-010)
    - Pin red and blue with printed photographs of Wilson and Marshall, with text: Vote for America First, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-011)
    - Pin white with American flag and text: United behind the President, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-012)
    - Pin with printed photographs of Wilson and Marshall with text: Wilson and Marshall, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-013)
    - Pin white, with portrait of Wilson with text: Win with Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-014)
    - Pin blue, with text: Wilson Kennedy Smith DeWitt, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-015)
    - Pin with blue border and printed photograph of Wilson with text: Safety first, the man of the eight hour day, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-016)
    - Pin with colorized portrait of Wilson with text: Woodrow Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-017)
    - Pin with blue border and printed photograph of Wilson with text: Progressive policies become law under Wilson, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-018)
    - Pin with blue and red border and American flag in shield, with text: America First, 1912 or 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW19xx-019)
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1928 or 1932
    - Button with printed photograph of Hoover and text: For President Herbert Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-001)
    - Pin with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-002)